Contact

+923111837500 (Mobile) nomannomi4545@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/noman-khalid-30bb48179 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills JavaScript HTML SQL

Noman Khalid

Asp.Net Core (Angular) Software Engineer | Microservices | Freelancer | Researcher

Islamabad

Summary

Having 4 plus years of experience in Web Development. Experienced Dotnet Software Developer with a substantiated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in .Net Core, Angular, Asp.Net MVC 5 with razor view, Boilerplate, Sql Server, Entity Framework, Microservices, Docker, Azure, Dapper, Nhibernate, Ado.Net. I also have experience in many popular libraries.

I have passionate to enhance my skills, abilities and knowledge for practical and real life situations. I have abality to work both individually and collaboratively with a team as a good team player.

Experience

azakaw Software Engineer April 2021 - Present (8 months) Islamabad, Islāmābād, Pakistan

Siqa Software Services (pvt) limited. Software Engineer January 2018 - April 2021 (3 years 4 months) Pakistan

Education

Arid Agriculture University

MS Computer Science, Computer Science · (September 2020 - August 2022)

Arid Agriculture University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2015 - 2019)